

Rodrigo

Developer



14 July 1983



Kaohsiung, Taiwan



+886 9 7005 2459



+886 9 8267 3010



http://goo.gl/F2v0o5



rodfersou@gmail.com

About me -

I am passionate about the art of creating computer programs.

As you can see by looking at my experience, I worry much more about building a solid foundation of knowledge than work just with a particular language. I consider myself able to accept the challenge of working in any environment, language, database or platform.



CSS

Design Patterns

Java

Javascript

Python

ReactJS

SOL

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 5 (Expert).]

interests

Good challenges, which demand concentration and focus on quality deliveries.

education

2011-2012 Web Development Specialization course. **UTFPR** Use of offline web pages in the inventory of assets process. 2008-2009 Software Engineering and Database Specialization course. UEL Generating code from a class diagram to an object-relational mapper. 2002-2006 Computer Engineering Graduation. UNOPAR Adaptive assistant to access classroom tools. 2000-2001 Data Processing Technical course. **CEETEPS** Development of a library management system.

experience

2018-Atual Senior Backend and Frontend Developer kitconcept GmbH Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone / ReactJS) 2015-2018 Team leader Simples Consultoria Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone) 2014-2015 Software architect Anicet Corporação Analysis and development of big data systems and generation of marketing information for e-commerce. (Python / MongoDB) 2012-2014 Developer AVADORA digital Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone) 2013-2014 Systems Analyst AGILI Softwares para Área Pública Analysis and development of systems and web portals. (CSharp / Oracle) 2011-2012 Senior Systems Analyst MÓDULOS RECAP SOFTWARE LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for tire retreaders. (Delphi / Firebird) 2011-2011 ABAP Developer PADO SA INDUST. COMERCIAL E IMPORTADORA Customization of SAP ERP screens and reports. (ABAP) 2009-2011 Systems Analyst Maxwell Bohr Instrumentação Eletrônica Development of applications for automation devices. (Python / C / C ++) 2009-2009 Systems Analyst Development and maintenance of application for automated processing of electronic texts. (Delphi / SQL Server) 2008-2009 Systems Analyst Onixsat Rastreamento de Veículos Ltda Development and maintenance of GPRS and Satellite messaging server. (CSharp / SQL Server) 2006-2008 Developer Amcor Flexibles Brasil LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for flexibles industry. (Progress 4GL)

languages

2003-2006 Senior Systems Analyst

(Progress 4GL)

English Understand Well, Speak Well, Read Well, Write Well. Spanish Understand Well, Speak Reasonably, Read Reasonably, Write Little. Japanese Understand Reasonably, Speak Little, Read Little, Write Little.

Development and maintenance of ERP for vehicle dealers.

Jabur Informática